And if this is scaring you a little bit,
we're going to go through this in with a
debugger once we've finished our last
line of code. So what we want to do now
is we know our arrow is the position
that we're sorting for. We want to move
the smallest thing to wherever the arrow
is. And we know we want to swap if
whatever is in the arrow position is
larger than whatever is in the box
position, meaning the one right next to
it or wherever the box happens to be. So
what we're going to do is we're going to
say if numbers
at the arrow position
is bigger than numbers at the box
position. Meaning if or is bigger than
one, then we want to swap those. Well,
now we can take advantage of our swap
logic. So let's copy that swap logic and
paste it down here. I'm going to hold
option shift and then F or alt shift F
on a Windows. And that will format my
code to make it neater and easier to
read. So I'm going to get a hold number.
The hold number is the number I'm taking
out. Well, which number am I taking out?
Well, the one I'm about to overwrite.
Well, if I want to swap one into the
four position, then I'm going to take
let's one would be in the box position.
So we're going to say our hold number is
the four that's about to get replaced.
So in other words, it's wherever our
arrow is.
Then we want to set our arrow position
equal to whatever was in the box that we
were comparing to. And then once we're
done, we're going to set the box equal
to the hold number. So, I'm going to
save this and I'm going to log numbers
at the end.
So, let's go to our console. We'll
reload and we get 1 2 3 4 5 6 which may
look like magic but I'm going to show
you how that works using the debugger.